<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Bill Vinson</title><link>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Bill Vinson</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://billvinson.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania</title><link>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/quantumania/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/quantumania/</guid><description>Let me just say that I do NOT understand what is going on with the reviews of Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania. Currently (the evening of 2023.02.17), Rotten Tomatoes has this movie sitting at a Tomatometer of 48%. That feels like an incredibly low percentage for a movie that I really enjoyed. That isn&amp;rsquo;t to say there aren&amp;rsquo;t issues to be had with this movie, but I found it to be lots of fun.</description></item><item><title>Stranger Things (Seasons 1-4)</title><link>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/stranger-things/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/stranger-things/</guid><description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t subscribed to Netflix for a bit as I feel they are overpriced for the content they offer. However, while I was caught up on Stranger Things, my younger son, Ian, was keen to watch it with me. The first two seasons didn&amp;rsquo;t particularly concern me as he isn&amp;rsquo;t easily frightened, but each season gets a bit more dark (similar in that respect to the Harry Potter series) and with seasons 3 and 4, I feel they crank up the gore and scares (compared to previous seasons).</description></item><item><title>Black Panther: Wakanda Forever</title><link>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/wakanda-forever/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/wakanda-forever/</guid><description>I went to see Black Panther: Wakanda Forever last night with my younger son and we both enjoyed it. However, I think I enjoyed it more than he did as it is a slow burn of a blockbuster (there&amp;rsquo;s more dialog and less action set pieces or at least it felt that way). There is a large amount of attention to handling grief (rightly so). The loss of Chadwick Boseman weighs heavily on so much of this film.</description></item><item><title>WWDC 2022 Wishlist</title><link>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/wwdc-2022-wishlist/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/wwdc-2022-wishlist/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is a collection of some improvements that I am hoping to see as part of WWDC 2022. Some are more likely than others, but they&amp;rsquo;re all things I wish to be undertaken by Apple&amp;hellip;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Nine Inch Nails 2022</title><link>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/nine-inch-nails-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://billvinson.github.io/blog/nine-inch-nails-2022/</guid><description>Heather and I got to go see Nine Inch Nails at the Red Hat Amphitheater last night for the opening stop of their 2022 tour. We haven’t been to this venue before. It’s on the smaller side as it only holds ~6k people. The actual performance was good, but I didn’t love everything about where we were in the venue. The people in our row were constantly coming and going which leads to a lot of distractions.</description></item></channel></rss>